Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
Oversize Materials - Series X.A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues and Owner's Manuals
Oversize Materials - Series IX.A: Juvenalia
Oversize Materials - Series X.B: Catalogues
Oversize Materials - Series X.C: Periodicals
Oversize Materials - Series X.D: Miscellaneous
Oversize Materials - Series X.E: Books
Separated Material
Some materials have been removed to general circulation, Fales Special Collections, Fales Downtown Collection and Fales American Collection. These items can be searched for in Bobcat, the bobst Library online catalog.
Removed to General Circulation
The American Federation of Arts, Bonnard 1972
Aragon, Louis Henri Matisse vol. I and II, 1971
The Art Institute of Chicago, Anselm Kiefer 1987
Barr, Alfred Jr. Matisse His Art and His Public 1951
Barron, Stephanie and Wolf-Dieter Dube German Expressionism 1951
Berlant, Anthony and Khlenberg Wake in Beauty: The Navaho and their Blankets 1977
Bosworth, Patricia Dianne Arbus a Biography 1984
Brettell, Richard R. Monet to Moore: The Millenium Gift of Sara Lee Corporation 1999
Bruce, Deborah The David Park Scroll 1989
Bucci, Mario Miro 1970
Busignani, Alberto Marini 1968
Cahill, James La Peinture Chinoise 1977
Cahill, James The Restless Landscape: Chinese Painting of the Late Ming Period 1971
Cairns, Huntington and John Walker eds. Great Paintings from the National Gallery of Art 1952
Carli, Enzo La "Maesta" di Duccio 1982
Carnduff Ritchie, Andrew Abstract Painting and Sculpture in America 1951
Carnegie Mellon University Art Gallery Elizabeth Murray Drawings 1980-1986 1986
Christian, John Symbolists and Decadents 1977
Cluny, Claude Michel La Poesie Francaise D'Humour 1970
Cogniat, Raymond Bonnard unnown date, ca. 1967
Cooper, Douglas The Cubist Epoch 1971
Debreczeny, Paul Alexander Pushkin: Complete Prose Fiction 1983
Downes, Rackstraw Fairfield Porter: Art in its Own Term. Selected Criticism 1935-1975 1979
Duerden, Dennis African Art 1968
Elderfield, John The "Wild Beast" Fauvism and its Affinities 1976
Elgar, Frank Picasso Blue and Pink Periods 1956
Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University Ingres Centennial Exhibition 1967
Fondo Editorial de la Plastica Mexicana Jose Guadalupe Posada: Ilustrador de la Vida Mexicana 1992
Forma, Warren Five British Sculptors 1964
Fradier, Georges Mosaiques Romaines de Tunisie 1992
Fundacio Joan Miro Centre d'Estudis d'Arte Comtemporani Art Tantric 1975
Gablik, Suzi Magritte 1985
Gallery of Masterpieces Giotto: Frescoes in the Upper Church, Assisi 1954
Gallery Yoshii Bonnard 1973
Gallery Yoshii Giorges Rouault 1976
Giotto: Portfolio of Reproductions 1944
Goldscheider, Ludwig Leonardo da Vinci: The Artist 1944
Gowing, Lawrence Turner: Imagination and Reality 1966
Grand Palais Henri Matisse 1970
Gurdjieff Views from the Real World: Early Talks 1973
Haas, Emily Bruce Davidson Brooklyn Gang 1999
Hanson, Anne Coffin Manet and the Modern Tradition 1979
Heusinger, Lutz Michelangelo: Complete Works undated
Hickey, Dave The Invisible Dragon: Four Essays on Beauty 1993
James Cohan Gallery Roxy Paine 2001
Kettlewell, James K. The Hyde Collection Catalogue 1981
Keilty, Bernadine Masters of Painting: Their Works, Their Lives, Their Times 1964
Leymarie, Jean Balthus 1982
Lipman, Jean Five Star Folk Art: One Hundred American Masterpieces 1990
Malevitch Suprematism: 34 Drawings 1974
Malingue, Maurice Paul Gaugin Letters to his Wife and Friends 1949
Malraux, Andre L'Intemporel 1976
Masini, Lara Vinca Braque 1971
Mauner, George Manet the Still-Life Paintings 2000
Meauze, Pierre African Art 1968
Mitchinson, David Henry Moore: Unpublished Drawings 1971
Monod-Fontaine, Isabelle and Marielle Tabart Brancusi 1977
Mourlot, Fernand Picasso Lithographs 1970
Museum of American Folk Art Expressions of a New Spirit: Highlights from the Permanent Collection 1989
Museum of Modern Art Masters of Modern Art 1954
Museum of Modern Art The Natural Paradise: Painting in America 1800-1950
Myers, Terry R. Robert Overby Parallel: 1978-1969 2000
National Gallery of Art, Washington An American Sampler: Folk Art from the Shelburne Museum 1987
O'Neill, John P. Ed. Mitsou 1984
Reunion des Musees Nationaux Le Siecle de Titien 1993
Rewald, Sabine Balthus 1984
Rogers, Howard Ed. China: 5,000 Years 1998
Rosenberg, Pierre Fragonard 1988
Ross, John G. and William H. Peck Egyptian Drawings 1978
Richardson, John Edouard Manet in Full Color 1969
Rossoli, Franco Modigliani 1959
Rouart, Denis and Jean-Dominique Rey Monet Water-Lilies 1974
Rubin, William ed. Cezanne: The Late Work 1977
Rubin, William Miro in the Collection of the Museum of Modern Art 1973
Rugoff, Milton Famous Artists Annual. A Treasury of Contemporary Art
Russell, Bertrand Mysticism and Logic 1917
St. Louis Art Museum Henri Matisse Paper Cut-Outs 1977
Schapiro, Meyer Vincent Van Gogh 1950
Schmied, Wieland Tobey 1966
School of Paris 1965
Scott, Curtis R. ed. Brancusi 1995
Scott, David John Sloan 1871-1951 1971
Shone, Richard Duncan Grant Designer 1980
Sickman, Laurence Great Chinese Painters of the Ming and Ch'ing Dynasties 1949
Skira, Albert ed. Carlo Carra 1996
Skira, Albert Manet unknown date
Smithsonian Goya Drawings and Prints 1955
The Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum Frantisek Kupka 1871-1957 1975
Sperone, Gian Enzo Il Mercante Altrove: Disegni da una Collezione 1996
Stebbins Jr. Theodore E. Martin Johnson Heade 1999
Strand, Mark The Contemporary American Poets: American Poetry since 1940 1969
Stuckey, Charles F. Claude Monet: 1840-1926
Sweeney, James Johnson Joan Miro 1970
Tantham, David Winslow Homer in the Adirondacks 1996
University Galleries of Illinois State University Contemporary American Painting 1951
Waldman, Diane Mark Rothko 1903-1970 A Retrospective 1978
Wattenmaker, Richard Art of Charle Prendergast 1978
Weekes, C.P. The Invincible Monet 1960
Wertenbaker, Leal The World of Picasso 1881 1967
Whitehead, Alfred North Modes of Thought 1938
Whitney Museum of American Art The Sculpture and Drawings of Elie Nadelman 1882-1946 1975
Wildenstein Goya 1950
Wildenstein la revue blanche 1983
Wildenstein Jubilee Loan Exhibition 1901-1951 Masterpieces from Museums and Private Collections
Wildenstein Maurice Utrillo 1883-1955 1957
Wildenstein Seurat and His Friends 1953
Removed To Fales American Collection
Allen, James, Hilton Als, Congressman John Lewis, Leon F. Litwack Without Sanctuary: Lynching Photography in America 2000
Calderone, Mary Steichen, Edward Steichen, John Updike The First Picture Book: Everyday Things for Babies
Dennis, Donna and Kenward Elmslie 26 Bars 1987
Removed to Fales Special Collections
Arenas, Roberto Triana and Sandro Chia Bestario 1980
Pal, Pratapaditya Court Paintings of Indai 16th-19th Centuries 1983
Vermeer, Jan Jan Vermeer of Delft: Portfolios of Great Masters 1925
Books Removed to Fales Downtown Collection
ACLU AIDS Project Epidemic of Fear: A Survey of AIDS Discrimination in the 1980s and Policy Recommendations for the 1990s 1990
Artists Space 25th Anniversary Limited Edition Card Collection, 1999
Baker, Rob The Art of AIDS: From Stigma to Conscience 1994 [This book includes Frank More cover art and chapter]
Bellamy, Peter The Artist Project. Portraits of the Real Art World: New York Artists 1981-1990 1991
Brainard, Joe More I Remember 1972
Brainard, Joe New Work 1973
Brainard, Joe Nothing to Write Home About 1981
Brainard, Joe and Kenward Elmslie Pay Dirt 1992
Brainard, Joe and Keward Elmslie Sung Sex 1989
Between Life and Death: Frank Moore 2002
Castle, Ted Three Americans Address the World 1981
Columbia Review: "The Referential Fallacy" by Riffaaterre, Poetry and Fiction Winter 1978
D'Agostino, Roberto Libidine: Guida Sintetica ad una vera Degenerazione Fisica e Morale 1987
Dion, Mark and Alexis Rockman Concrete Jungle: A Pop Media Investigation of Death and Survival in Urban Ecosystems 1996
DPN: Diseased Pariah News #7 1992, #9 1994, #10 1995
Dugdale, John Lengthening Shadows Before Nightfall 1995
Eggleston, William 2 1/4 1999
Finkelpearl, Tom Dialogues in Public Art 2000 [Includes interview with Frank Moore]
Friedman, Michael Distinctive Belt 1985
Gilbert and George Side by Side 1971
Giorno, John Balling Buddha 1970
Giorno, John you got to burn to shine 1994
Gooch, Brad The Daily News 1977
Gooch, Brad Jailbait and Other Stories 1984
Gould, Claudia and Valerie Smith 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: 25 Years 1998
Ginsberg, Allen Allen Ginsberg Photographs 1990
Hendricks, Geoffrey The Fertility of the Soil 1992
Holly Solomon Gallery: The First Two Years 1977
Hornick, Lita and Poet Friends To Elizabeth and Eleanor: Great Queens Who Loved Poetry 1993
Kakania, Konstantin Freedom or Death
LeSueur, Joe You were a bastard for being so fucking good in bed, or The Unmentionable, 1982
Lippard, Lucy R. Pop Art 1966
The Manipulator Issue #2, 1984
Muller, Gregoire and Gianfranco Gargoni The New Avant-garde: Issues for the Art of the Seventies 1972
New Observations #8, 1983
Oldenburg, Claes Notes in Hand 1971
Rockman, Alexis Guyana 1996
Russo, Vito The Celluloid Closet: Homosexuality in the Movies Revised Edition, 1987
Sarfati, Patrick Athletes 1990
Sarfati, Patrick Illusions: photographies 1985
Seidner, David The Face of Contemporary Art 1996
Shaw, Jim Thrift Store Paintings 1990
Shiney International #2, 1987
Solomon, Alan and Ugo Mulas New York: The New Art Scene 1967
Susan Mini Mag vo. 1 Winter Solstice, vol. 2 Spring Equinox ca. 1992
Taschen, Benedikt Tom of Finland 1992
Top Stories, a Prose Periodical #19-20 Cookie Mueller, How to Get Rid of Pimples, 1984
Tracks: A Journal of Artists' Writings 3:3 Fall 1977
True Homosexual Experiences from S.T.H.: Flesh vol. 2, 1982
White, Edmund Loss Within Loss: Artists in the Age of AIDS 2001
Winters, Terry Ocular Proofs
Wong, Martin Eureka 1976 [inscribed to Frank Moore by artist]
Catalogues Removed to Fales Downtown Collection
Abstract Implosionism, February 2-February 10, Ted Greewald Gallery Inc. New York
"American Bricolage" November 2- December 22 Sperone Westwater, New York
Jan Aronson, undated
Arts' Communicties/AIDS Communities: Realizing the Archive Project, February 20-March 3, 1996 Cyclorama, Boston
Bellamy, Peter. The Artist Project Information
Bellamy, Peter. New Portraits from teh Artist Project, October 29-November 23, 1985, Jack Tilton Gallery, New York
Bid for LIfe: A Tribute to Robert C. Wooley June 26, 1995 Sotheby's, New York
Brainard, Joe. Retrospective, March 20-April 19, 1997. Tibor de Nagy Gallery, New York
Chaet, Bernard. February 26-April4, 1998. New York Studio School of Drawing, Painting and Sculpture
Alan E. and Ellen Cober Collection, September 28-October 31, 1995. Giampietro, New York
Concurrencies, an exhibition curated by Lucio Pozzi and William Chambers, December 10-January 9, 1993. Grace Borgenicht Gallery, New York
Connelly, Chuck. April 17-May 11, 1997. Alexandre de Folin, New York
Cooper Union Museum. Recent Acquisitions, 1964
Creative Time: 1989-1990.
Creative Time: 1991-1992. 1993, New York
Dugdale, John. Special Portfolio of Platinum Prints, 1996. Wessel O'Connor Gallery, New York
Episalla, Joy. inside/out. September 9-October 9, 1999. Debs and Co. New York
Episalla, Joy. Removed. February 15-March 23, 2002. Debs and Co. New York
Falk, Gary. A Monograph, Feb 8, 1954. October 1, 1986 New York.
Fazzolari, Bruno. Today is the Tomorrow You Worried About Yesterday. February 17-March 25, 2000, Debs and Co. New York.
The Figure as Fiction: The Figure in Visual Art and Literature. Curated by Alaine A. King. December 3, 1993-January 23, 1994. The Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati
From Media to Metaphor: Art About AIDS. Robert Atkins and Thomas W. Sokolowski guest curators. September-October 1993, Grey Art Gallery adn Study Center, New York University
Graham, Rodney and bruc Nauman. "...the nearest faraway place..." May 10, 2000-Spring 2001, Dia Center for the Arts, New York City.
Guston, Philip. Small Paintings and Drawings 1968-1980. March 2000, McKee Gallery, New York
Hammond, Jane. Back Stage-Secrets of Scene Painting. January 18-April 5, 2002. Whitney Museum of American Art at Philip Morris.
Hammond, Jane. From Avatar to Zed. September 29-October 27, 2001. Galerie Lelong, New York
Hammond, Jane. The John Ashbery Collaboration. December 13 2001- March 3, 2002. Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art
Hammond, Jane. The John Ashbery Collaboration. Jose Freire Fine Art Inc, New York
Hannah, Duncan. Arrivals and Departures. September 18-October 18, 1997. Tibor de Nagy Gallery, New York
Hannah, Duncan. First Love and Other Paintings. October 12-November 11, 1995. Tibor de Nagy Gallery, New York
Heap of Birds, Hachivi Edgar. Claim Your Color. September 8-May 6, 1990. Exit Art, New York.
Heiferman, Marvin adn Carole Kismaric. Paradise Now: Picturing the Genetic Revolution. September 9-October 20, 2000. Exit Art New York. [Includes essay by Frank Moore]
Holliday, Frank. Wah-Wah Series. Debs and Co. New York
Honsby, Rob. Anniversary. Debs and Co. New York
Humphrey, David. Love Teams: Paintings 1996-1997. March 20-April 18, 1998, Zolla Leiberman Gallery Inc.
Joelson, Suzanne. Family. November 19-December 19, 1998. Debs and Co. New York
Juarez, Roberto. The Entered The Road. January 3-July 1, 1995. Center for the Fine Arts. Miami
Kaplowitz, Jane. Recent Paintings. March 25-May 1, 1993. Jason McCoy Inc. New York
Katchadourain, Nina Talking Popcorn, Paranormal Postcards, and Indecision on the Moon January 13-February 24 2001 at Debs and Co.
Kortick, Roy. (Masters of the Impossible) MOTI. Debs and Co. New York
Krasner, Lee. Paintings from the Late Fifties. October 26-November 20, 1982. Robert Miller Gallery, New York
Kuitca, Guillermo. Poema Peagogico. Sperone Westwater, New York
Lerner, Marily, David Provan, Kris Ruhs, Lynton Wells, Terry Zupanc. Invitational. 1990. Grace Borgenicht Gallery, New York.
Lincoln, Paul Etienne. A Violet Somnambulist Spiriting the Fugacious Bloom: An Investigation into Ignisfatuus and its mechanisms of memory. March 11-April 15, 2000. Alexander adn Bonin, New York
Lionni, Leo. Parallel Botany, Sculptures and Drawings. October 11-November 5, 1977. Staempfli, New York
The Machine as Seen at the End of the Mechanical Age. Museum of Modern Art, New York
Marden, Brice. 1975. Guggenheim Museum, New York
Martin, Chris. Long Lake and In the Lake. February 1-March 31, 2001. Malca Fine Art, New York
Martin, Chris. April 4028. Pierogi, Brooklyn New York.
Metz, Mike. 12 Monuments. January 9-27. 55 Mercer Gallery, New York
Montanez Ortiz, Rafael. Years of the Warrior 1960, Years of teh Psyche 1988. March 26-May 22, 1988. Museo del Barrio, New York
Negroponte, George. Recent Paintings. March 8-April 22, 1995. Mason McCoy Inc New York
Nelson, David. 2000. Debs and Co. New York
Neshat, Shirin. Turbulent. October 23, 1998-January 15, 1999. Whitney Museum of American Art at Philip Morris.
Nudo and Crudo. January 25-March 16, 1996. Claudia Gina Ferrari Art Contemporanea, Milan.
Pardo, Jorge. Project. September 13-June 17, 2001. Dia Center for the Arts, New York City
Pictures, an exhibition of the work of Try Brauntuch, Jack Goldstein, Sherrie Levine, Robert Longo, Philip Smith. September 24-October 29, 1977. Artists Space. New York
Pierre et Gilles. December 6, 1990-January 8, 1991. Hirschl adn Adler Modern, New York
Prospect 96 Potographie der Gegenwartskunst. March 9-May 12, 1996
Redon, Odilon. Selections from the Woodner Family Collection. April 9-May 28, 1993. The Drawing Center.
Rooms. June 9-26, 1976. P.S. 1, New York
Rotick, Roy. New Paintings. October 15-November 14, 1998. Debs and Co. New York
Row, David. 1993. John GOod Gallery, New York
Salle, David. January 14- March 29, 1987. Whitney Museum of American Art, New York
Sandrow, Hope. Water of Life. July 24-October 9, 1988. Whiteny Museum of American Art at Philip Morris.
Senser, Andreas. Selected Works by Andreas Senser.
Serios, Ted. Phenomena: A Selection of Photographs. Marta Cervera Gallery, New York
Sillman, Amy. February 27-April 4, 1998. Casey Kaplan, New York
di Suvero, Mark. November 13, 1875-February 8, 1976. Whitney Museum of American Art, New York.
Tapies, Antonio. Objects from the Early Seventies. November 18-December 30, 19xx. Marta Cervera Gallery, New York
Telfair, Tula. Constructed Landscapes: Series III and IV. April 9-May 16, 1998. DFN Gallery, New York
Tufte, Edward. Visual Explanations: Prints and Sculptures. November 11, 2000-January 13, 2001. Artists Space, New York
Tzaig, Uri. Duel. September 9-October 28, 2000. Artists Space New York
Usle, Juan. 22 Riviera Blue, 40 Ruby. November 12-December 19, 1992. John Good Gallery, New York.
Visual AIDS in collaboration with Real Art Ways. Bodies of Resistance, curated by Barbara Hunt. December 1, 1999-January 30, 2000 in Hartford Connecticut. July 2-20, 2000 at Interntional AIDS Conference, Durban, South Africa.
Wasserman, Jeffrey. 1986. Daniel Newburg Gallery.
Wasserman, Jeffrey. Virtual Garrison. New York.
Weatherford, Mary. Easter. March 28-April 29, 1998. Debs and Co. New York
Wegman, William. Why Draw? March-April, 1990. Sperone Westwater, New York.
Whitney Museum of American Art. 1995 Biennial Exhibition. [includes Frank Moore's Art]
Whitney Museum of American Art. The Power of the City, The City of Power. 1991-1992
Yamaoka, Carrie. (t)here. January 6-February 12, 2000. Debs and Co, New York.
ZG Breakdown issue
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Sound recordings.; Moving images.; Video recordings.; Painters -- United States.; Clippings (information artifacts); Financial records; France.; Genetic engineering |x Moral and ethical aspects.; Genetic engineering |x Environmental aspects.; Experimental films; United States.; Notebooks; Found objects.; Photographs.; Fliers (printed matter); Sketchbooks.; Correspondence.; Picture postcards.; AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Self, Jim, 1954-; Moore, Rebecca; Primary Performance Group; Gesso Foundation; Moore, Frank, 1953-2002; Episalla, Joy; Fulps, Robert
- Series I: Notebooks, 153679
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains Frank Moore's art notebooks and sketchpads. Materials are organized in loose chronological order as established by the Gesso Foundation.
  - Notebook #1, 1971-1975; 153830 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042232390
  - Notebook #2, 1974-1975; 153829 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #3, 1971-1975; 153828 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197081 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #5, 1975; 153827 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Loose items from Notebook #5, 1975; 153826 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Notebook #6, 1975; 153825 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Loose items from Notebook #6, 1975; 153824 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notebook #7, 1975-1976; 153823 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Notebook #8, 1976; 153822 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197082 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197; 153821 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Notebook #10, 1976; 153820 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Notebook #11, March-June 1976, 153819 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Loose items from Notebook #11, March-June 1976, 153818 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Notebook #12, 1976; 153817 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Loose items from Notebook #12, 1976; 153816 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Notebook #13, 1976; 153815 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Loose items from Notebook #13, 1976; 153814 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Notebook #14, ca. 1976; 153813 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Loose items from Notebook #14, ca. 1976; 153812 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Notebook #15, 1977; 153811 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Loose items from Notebook #15, 1977; 153810 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Notebook #16, 1977; 153809 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Loose items from Notebook #16, 1977; 153808 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Notebook #17, 1977; 153807 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Loose items from Notebook #17, 1977; 153806 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Notebook #18, 1977; 153805 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Loose items from Notebook #18, 1977; 153804 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Notebook #19, 1977-1979; 153803 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Loose items from Notebook #19, 1977-1979; 153802 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Notebook #20, 1977-1979; 153801 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042232408
  - Loose items from Notebook #20, 1977-1979; 153800 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197083 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Notebook #22, 1978-1979; 153799 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Loose items from Notebook #22, 1978-1979; 153798 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Notebook #23, ca. 1977-1979; 153797 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Loose items from Notebook #23, 1977-1979; 153796 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Notebook #24, 1979-1980; 153795 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Loose items from Notebook #24, 1979-1980; 153794 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Notebook #25, 1979-1980; 153793 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197084 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197085 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197086 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197087 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Loose items from Notebook # 28, 1978-1980; 153792 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Notebook #29, 1979-1980; 153791 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Notebook #30, 1979-1980; 153790 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Loose items from Notebook #30, 1979-1980; 153789 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Item removed to oversize, 153788 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Notebook #32, 1980; 153787 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Loose items from Notebook #32, 1980; 153786 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Notebook #33, 1980; 153785 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Loose items from Notebook #33, 1980; 153784 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Notebook #34, 1980-1981; 153783 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Notebook #35, 1980-1981; 153782 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Loose items from Notebook #35, 1980-1981; 153781 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197088 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Notebook #37, 1980-1982; 153780 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Notebook #38, 1981; 153779 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Loose items from Notebook #38, 1981; 153778 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Notebook #39, 1981; 153777 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Loose items from Notebook #39, 1981; 153776 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197089 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Loose items from Notebook #40, 1981; 153775 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197090 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197091 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197092 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Loose items from Notebook #43, 1981-1982; 153774 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197093 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197094 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Notebook #45, 1982; 153773 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Loose items from Notebook #45, 1982; 153772 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Notebook #46, 1982; 153771 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Loose items from Notebook #46, 1982; 153770 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Notebook #47, 1982; 153769 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Loose items from Notebook #47, 1982; 153768 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Notebook #48, 1982-1983; 153767 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042232416
  - Loose items from Notebook #48, 1982-1983; 153766 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Notebook #49, 1981-1983; 153765 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Loose items from Notebook #49, 1982-1983; 153764 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Notebook #50, 1982-1983; 153763 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197095 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Notebook #52, 1983; 153762 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Loose items from Notebook #52, 1983; 153761 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Notebook #53, 1983-1984; 153760 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Notebook #54, 1983; 153759 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Notebook #55, 1983-1984; 153758 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Loose items from Notebook #55, 1983-1984; 153757 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Notebook #56 titled "Hybrid Notebook", 1984-1994; 153756 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Loose items from Notebook #56, 1984-1994; 153755 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Notebook #57, 1984; 153754 (Box 3, Folder 92)